Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Episode 93
Osman Bey Headquarters
My Sheik.
My brother.
Sir, what is our state?
What is our state, General?
It is that Turks came all the way down
to our door.
But they won't be able to enter.
This is my castle!
And it will remain as mine!
Close the bridge!
My Beys!
My Alps!
Everything waits for its time in this
world!
Inegöl did the same!
The seed we planted sprouted and grew!
Now it is on the verge of becoming
a big plane tree!
It stretches out its branches to the sky!
Alps! Beys!
We will either take Inegöl or be martyred!
It is war time!
Allah is one!
Yell as much as you can!
I will crucify you all from your tongue!
But Osman first!
For that, you will fisrt have to win,
Nikola.
Allah is one!
Do you hear them?
Do you?
This is the Turks' sound!
Allah is one!
Do you know what they want from me?
My castle!
They want my city!
They are thirsty for your blood!
Our blood!
This isn't the first flow of my
blood, it won't be the last.
They are outside! Watching our castle!
Then, with the arrows we shoot, we will
rip out not only their eyes looking at...
...our castle, but also the lungs of
their women and children!
no matter how strong their armies are...
... no matter how much ammunition
they have...
...no matter how devastating they are...
...we won't fall down!
One of us can beat a thousand of them!
One of us can beat a thousand!
Brave children of Byzantium!
Some of you will die.
But we will die with honor, by fighting!
We will die like heroes!
You will get thousands of hits!
We will get thousands of hits!
Our necks will be hit by arrows, our
chests will be hit by daggers!
But...
...mothers and fathers will tell their
children about...
...the bravery, the honor of the soldiers
in this castle!
They will tell about your heroism
for centuries!
Mothers, fathers, families...
...maybe will name your children...
...as you, you and maybe you!
And I...
...Aya Nikola...
...I swear on my honor and dignity that...
I will protect my city, my castle,
my people and you...
...until the last drop of my blood!
Rome is greater than Turks!
And it will remain so!
Brave children of Byzantium!
The name of the Turks will be erased
from these lands today!
Long live Great Rome!
Death to the Turks!
We know well about the weakness of
their walls.
We will keep hitting day and night
until we break it.
The rest of the catapults will keep
hitting the bastions of the castle.
But as we go in through the broken wall...
...I don't want to see even one bow
aimed at our way.
As you order, my Bey.
Let's go.
Bring it.
-In the name of Allah!
My Bey! My Bey! My Bey!
Make way! My Bey!
My Bey!
You know that Akça Dervish worked
very hard for this.
He died in my arms.
He couldn't see these days.
He told Master Davut that...
...if he can't see the conquest, let his
sword see it.
Send it with the first cannon.
Brother.
Akça.
The valiant's bone melts, but his name
remains!
It will be as he said.
Bring it.
In the name of Allah!
My Allah...
...this is for Shepherd Akça.
Nothing can stop him!
In the name of Allah!
It is time!
Alps!
Brothers!
Allah!
Allah is one!
This way!
Careful!
Now!
Come on, brothers!
Come on!
Load it!
Allah is one!
Come on!
God, protect us from the wrath of
the Turks and...
...the stupidity of those who rule Rome!
Come on, lions!
Come on, valiants!
Allah is one!
Welcome to hell, Osman Bey!
Welcome!
Unlike us, Osman does not waste any time!
Look at the castle!
Do you see this?
I do, Romanos! I do!
Osman is only raising the fire he lit!
That's it!
I will burn him and those who love him
so bad that...
...when this fire ends...
...only thing remaining from the Turks
will be their ashes!
Ashes! That's all!
I wish my father let us and we could
come with you, Kumral Abdal.
We could at least help the wounded Alps,
Kumral Abdal.
We can't sit here while the alps are on
the battlefield.
Come on!
My brave Shahzadas!
Now, it is our turn.
After us, it will be your turn.
Patience. Patience.
Since Bala Hatun became the leader of the
hatuns they have never missed a target!
Bala Hatun was raised by Sheik Edebalı.
And with Aygül Hatun...
From now on is on Aygül and sisters.
Conquest is deserved by who work.
I hope you all can experience it.
I hope so.
I will convey your trust to the alps.
Holofira will set off tomorrow.
You've protected me. I am grateful to you.
What is it?
It was my mother's necklace.
It is beautiful.
My Fatma!
Oh, my beautiful daughter!
My beautiful daughter!
My Fatma, what are you doing here?
Are you all right?
He neither ate nor drank. We had to
bring her, Malhun Hatun.
My beautiful daughter!
Welcome, my beautiful girl.
A painful death will meet you when
you eat these.
You will be held by the dark.
People are coming!
Since my daughter is beside me now,
I am relieved.
I know, my sister.
Missing a child is something else.
Thankfully you met your child.
I will be as happy as you when Osman Bey
and Barkın returns.
They will, of course.
Don't worry, sister.
I hope so, Sister.
You did a great job in this short time,
Alaca.
Come on, alps!
Load these to the carriages.
We will set off in the morning tomorrow.
Come on.
I told you there will be no winner in
a war!
Here we are, losing.
They lose because they kill and we lose
because we die.
Starting this war was a huge mistake.
Unfortunately, Lord Nikola was the one
to make this mistake.
He started this war.
And he sent us to the fire even
if he didn't want to.
Lord Nikola is fighting for us.
-Are you defending the Turks?
-What are you saying?
Of course I don't!
But, brothers, Lord Nikola worked for this
war to happen.
Look where we are now!
If you don't have the power to fight
the enemy...
...we must open our arms for hugs,
not for fists!
I know that if we approach the Turks with
good intentions...
...they will approach us the same way.
Their intention is not to destroy us.
If Lord Nikola started this war...
...he should bear the consequences alone.
We won't fight. We will be friends.
Entering a war that we will lose will only
increase our pain.
Osman wants to take the castle.
Do you think he will let us live if he
takes the castle?
-No! Not happening!
-No way!
-No way! We will fight!
-They will kill us!
Get off!
If Osman takes the castle...
...you will be next to die after Nikola.
I don't think so.
The Turks will never do anything to a man
of religion that has no harm.
I know them much better than you.
Is this why you speak against Lord Nikola?
Our soldiers have been watching you for
a while.
Your tongue will cause you big trouble,
Priest.
We are taking you to the dungeon by
the order of Lord Nikola.
-No, we won't let you take him!
-He has done nothing! No way!
-You can't take him!
-We won't let you take him!
Enough!
Our dungeons are big enough!
Does anyone want to rebel?
Good.
Tie him.
Allah is one!
Allah hears those who praise Him!
May Allah's peace, mercy and blessings
be upon you.
Oh our Mighty and Forever Allah!
This army only kneels to you.
They fear neither death nor injury.
Our Prophet calls this army veteran.
They are heroes from the heart.
They are all Turkish warriors.
O, Mightiest of All!
May you grant your prophet Muhammad
Mustafa a comrade...
...to this army.
Amen!
Grant so that the infidels can't defeat
the warriors of the Right!
-Amen!
Grant us Muhammad Mustafa...
...as their comrade so that...
...your great name can be heard all over
the world.
-Amen!
O, the Victorious!
May you grant our army the victory.
-Amen!
May you make their victory permanent!
Amen! Surah El-Fatiha!
Inegöl Castle
So, Lord Nikola is the one to blame.
Is that so?
No one can harm this city as much as
Nikola.
If you don't attack Turks, they will
approach you friendly.
But Nikola is a savage.
None of us matter to him.
Neither are you.
You'll regret what you said, Pristo.
Will I regret what I said?
Is he going to kill me?
Is he going to torture me?
What else can he do to me?
I'll take care of this
disrespectful priest.
Your poisonous tongue...
...makes Lord Nikola
very angry, Priest Prisso.
I'm afraid that will lead to your demise.
I am not afraid of Nikola.
He already killed the entire
city by starting this war.
Instead of seeing Nikola in İnegöl...
...I would rather live under
the auspices of Osman Bey.
I know of his and his father's mercy.
It seems it'll take a while for
this priest to come to his senses.
You guys leave.
I said leave!
If you want to stay
alive, stay quiet, priest.
Or, you won't get out of here alive.
Stay quiet and wait.
Just wait.
How could this happen?
You're better off not knowing anything.
Therefore, don't ask
any questions either.
Osman is hitting us
with everything he has.
Even I can't save you
after this mess, Nikola.
My soldiers are waiting for my
command outside and I'm stuck here.
Do you see those soldiers, Romanos?
They're all good at what they do.
They're going to protect
our walls, don't worry.
Osman and those shepherd alps...
...will be sorry they were born.
Be real Nikola, be real.
This is not a Khan battle.
The weapons, equipments...
...and an army is waiting
to kill you outside.
Your soldiers are strong,
I'll give you that...
...but don't underestimate Osman.
If this siege keeps on longer...
...he'll get the upper hand.
Do you think I haven't thought
those things through, Romanos?
For years, I've been thinking
of this, day in and day out!
Do you know what is one of the major
things that make a siege a failure?
Famine. If your are left hungry...
...you'll never and I mean never succeed.
That's why our warehouses
are full of food.
But,...
But if a disease starts spreading
amongst the people...
...you won't have anything else to do.
Exactly, Romanos.
That's why he have enough
ammuniton for Osman.
But it is an epidemic disease.
An epidemic disease.
I Aya Nikola, Romanos, took preacutions.
They won't know that hit them.
Hell is coming for you.
Allahu Akbar!
We've been hitting them since daytime.
The shots keep hitting them
without stopping, Osman Bey.
Pull!
Die!
Allahu Akbar!
We've been hitting them all day...
...but could not breach once.
We'll accomplish our goals with the
strength and the patience from Allah.
Patience will get us what
we aim to achieve, Turgut Bey.
We will breach the walls
of İnegöl, if Allah permits.
If Allah permits.
There is no turning back.
İnegöl will belong to the Turks.
Well said, Osman Bey!
We will be patient but it would
be better if we could breach soon.
What are we going to do if we fail?
We're exposed here to the enemy.
Barkın Bey is right, the
siege may take months.
What if the emperor sends an army?
İnegöl is full of food and water,
they can endure us for months.
Even Mongolians can get the
word and come after us from here.
One has to come to a conquest with faith.
But it is not the time to
make you have faith.
I don't tell anyone to stay or go.
But if anyone has doubt...
...they don't need to follow me.
Never, Osman Bey.
There is neither doubt nor fear among us.
We will follow you.
We came to the walls of İnegöl for
the establishment of a government.
We came here to drink
the sherbet of martrydom.
As we decided with Gündüz Bey...
...we will get the catapults
in front of the walls.
And Gündüz Bey will keep
hitting them, with patience.
We will hit them with
the wrath of the Turks.
With the belief of Allah.
We will have the breaches
that will make İnegöl our land.
Do not forget...
...it is not the strength of the
arrow that cracks the shield...
...it is the quantity of it.
I'd like to lead the alps when
the breaches are open, my Bey.
Whoever goes in first goes down quickly.
Therefore, after going in, you should
counter the attack as you go in.
My bey,...
...if you allow it, I'd like
to go in with Konur.
Of course, you may go in.
May Allah bless you, my bey!
We will be the first ones to plant
the bloody and glorious flag of İnegöl.
İnegöl is at the paw of the
wolf, there is no turning back.
We will be victorious for our government.
Let's burn the infidels, brothers!
Come on my lions, light it up!
Load it up!
Nikola!
Allahu Akbar!
Let's throw these fires at
the infidels, my brothers!
Soldiers!
Soldier! Soldiers!
Soldiers of Byzantine!
Sons of Byzantine, don't you dare dying
before bloodying up your swords!
If your swords are
not riddled with blood...
...I will kill you with my sword!
Archers, get to your positions!
Get to your positions!
Don't fall down!
Don't fall down, for
your castle, for Rome!
For Rome! Come on!
Let's go!
Osman!
We don't blindly get stubborn.
We do what we say we want to do.
If the siege draws out, we'll
be prepared accordingly.
How, Osman Bey?
We will make sure no one
comes for the aid of İnegöl.
Rahman Bey,...
...in order to stop the
aid coming from İznik...
...you'll be positioned at
Köprühisar with your alps.
May Allah bless you, Osman Bey!
Whoever helps the cruel deserves to die.
May Allah bless you!
Durmuş Bey, you take a position
in Akhisar with your valiants.
Until İnegöl belongs to Islam...
...we won't let anyone
get near it, Osman Bey.
May Allah bless you!
Barkın Bey,...
...you get one of your best alps
and divide into two groups.
You and your alps get
positioned in Adranus.
The rest will get in
position in Koyunhisar.
May Allah bless you, Osman Bey!
Come on, get on the road before sunset.
May Allah protect you!
May Allah bless you!
Allahu Akbar!
May I come in, my bey?
Come in, Hüsamettin, come.
You will send word to Nikola immediately.
The castle is under siege, my bey.
Do we need to go to the castle
to send word, Hüsamettin?
You will walk about twenty
steps from the left of Kızılağaç.
When you get to the right location,
look at the edge of the castle.
You will throw this arrow
to where the two flags stand.
A soldier is waiting for you there.
- Come on, go.
- Yes, my bey!
My men are waiting here.
We will surround there headquarters
as soon as the explosions start.
They will be crushed.
Their headquarters will be destroyed.
Sir, a word from one of
the spies amongst them.
Looks like your birds sent
you some good news, Nikola.
Very good news, Romanos.
Osman scattered the ones
that came from different tents.
So that they could protect
the important areas.
On top of that, he said some
of his own men with them.
I mean, Osman's army
is unguarded, Romanos.
Good.
I'll get on the move
immediately to lead my men.
As soon as I unite with them,
I'll attack their post.
When their post collapses, I
will burn all of their catapults.
Osman won't be amount to
anything without his catapults.
Also, he won't have a post
to position his army at.
He will be in trouble.
As you are assaulting Osman's post, I will
send all my soldiers to where Osman is.
The only difficulty...
...will be me going to Karasu
through the secret creek bed...
...when Osman and his men
are this near to the walls.
Take some brave men with you.
Get on the road.
Give just three brave men...
...so that I can destroy an
army of three thousand for you.
But make sure you're guys are ruthless.
Captain Romanos,...
...sir, they attacked
our honor in Bilecik.
Now, you're going to kill them.
Let me come with you.
Both dying and killing along
side you is an honour, sir!
May peace and mercy
of Allah be upon you!
Creator of all the almighty Allah,...
...master of all, the almighty Allah,...
...I pray to you to protect
me from the enemy...
...you are the mightiest.
My Allah,...
...I pray to you for the
protection of my son Aktemur,...
...my brother Osman, my innocent
nephews, and all Turmens...
...dear Allah.
Protect them from the devil and
from our enemies, dear Allah!
My Allah,...
...protect my son Aktemur...
...have him be your follower.
Make him a son befitting...
...Islam and his forefathers,
make him an alp!
They say the prayer of
the father for his son...
...is similar to the prayer of
prophet Muhammed's for ummah.
I am content with my child, dear Allah.
May he be a worthy servant to you.
Amen!
May I come in, Gündüz Bey?
Come in, Cerkutay.
- May Allah accept your prayer, my bey!
- May Allah bless you!
I sent the picket alps
as you wished, my bey.
Thank you, Cerkutay!
Thank you!
Your mind is at Aktemur, right, my bey?
Yes.
Having a child is sometihng else.
Ever since I've had kids, even
my sleeps are different, my bey.
My mind and my heart are always with them.
May Allah protect our children!
Amen!
Let's reunite with them safely as
soon as possible, if Allah permits.
If Allah permits.
If Allah permits, Cerkutay.
Inshallah(if Allah permits), my valiant.
Once we conquer İnegöl...
I'll unite with my Aktemur and
you'll unite with your children.
Don't worry.
Amin.
I don't worry, my bey.
Saltuk takes care of his siblings.
Should we go?
We should, Cerkutay.
İnegöl Castle
In front of the Northern Walls
With All Mighty Allah's
approval...
raise it!
Release it!
Release!
Brother.
Tell me what's bothering you.
I have nothing but the haste
of conquest, Osman Bey.
My only prayer is for this
hole to be opened.
Brother, whatever bothers you...
can be seen through your face.
Tell me.
Tell me, brother.
It's obvious that you are hiding it.
My child.
Aktemur.
What is his condition?
He is inside, Osman.
All alone.
Among all those demons.
What if he gets exposed?
Don't worry, brother.
Nothing will happen.
Be at ease.
Aktemur is like a wolf among
dogs now.
There is no enemy that can
deal with him.
Don't worry.
He is an undefeated alp,
just like his father.
Tell me.
What heathen ever stroke you?
The concerns I have can't
be controlled that simply.
I understand your concern, brother.
Love for your children...
is the biggest weakness a father
can have.
And the most beautiful one.
Remember it.
My father Ertuğrul Ghazi loved us.
My children, he would say.
My children are my greatest treasury.
Then he would commit us to each other.
Do you remember?
Yes.
Would I forget, brother?
He would say, you are two branches
of a sacred three.
And he would trust Allah and us
to protect one another.
Brother, don't worry.
Today is the day of conquest.
As Allah protects us, and we protect
each other...
Aktemur will be the same.
Our father sow a seed to
these lands.
We made it green.
Inshallah, our children will make that
sycamore root to the whole world...
with the same bravery and ambition.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
We came for jihad.
We lived for jihad.
We can die happily for it.
Give me your blessing.
It's yours, brother.
You too.
It's yours.
My pretty Holafira.
You reminded us Mari with
your arrival...
now your departure is harder.
I'm sad too.
I'm so curious about Mari.
I wish I could listen to
her story.
My pretty girl.
This is your home now.
If you don't like it there and
feel unhappy...
our doors will always be open.
And we'll tell you about Mari.
She was our sister.
And you became our daughter.
Come again, will you?
You are looking for my
brother Orhan, I know it.
But he isn't good with farewells.
Godspeed, Holafira.
I'm grateful, Alahaddin.
Can you tell Orhan too?
I will, Holafira.
Godspeed.
Holafira!
Go in peace.
Take care of yourself.
Goodbye, Orhan.
Come on, Sisters!
We'll company the carts.
I could send them with
the sisters.
We should take today's provisions
with Malhun, Aygül.
You take care of the sisters
drilling.
Prepare them until they get
ready for battle.
They should be ready when needed.
Don't worry.
It's good that someone stays
in the tribe.
We are at war.
Be cautious.
Children are under your protection.
Our children and tribe
are under our protection.
Don't worry.
Godspeed.
Ayşe Hatun.
The women should continue
after a rest.
I told them but they don't
want to rest.
They say that battle is a wedding
for the Kayı.
We don't get tired, they say.
Valiant women of the Kayı!
Mashallah.
May Allah bless them.
Inshallah.
Come on.
May Allah protect you.
Be careful.
Come on.
Come on!
May Allah bless our jihad.
Amin.
With Allah's approval,
I want to see the end of this war.
Oh, my Ayşe.
I understand you the best.
I know. You think about
Aktemur.
Your valiant is growing his renown.
Right?
Mashallah.
With Allah's approval,
he'll return safe and sound.
Inshallah, Aygül.
Inshallah.
My bey.
Aktemur.
News from Aktemur.
Mashallah!
Brother.
Aktemur does his duty well.
Be proud of your child.
Thank you.
Look at our valiant!
How did he send it, Osman Bey?
Commander Alexander.
We need to be faster.
Commander Romanos won't like us
being late.
I'll do many other things that Commander
Romanos won't like.
According to my nephew Aktemur...
Romanos will take his soldiers at Karasu
and attack us at the dawn.
At the same time...
Nikola will also get out of the castle
and attack us.
They are trying to set a trap, huh?
Let them!
We have enough valiants
to overcome anything.
Especially, yours, brother Gündüz!
Mashallah to my nephew Aktemur!
Thank you, Turgut Bey.
Thank you.
Osman Bey.
This Romanos seems to be smart.
Not many know that Karasu valley.
My bey.
They attack when the other tribe
beys leave.
Then, someone leaked
information.
Then, we have a traitor.
As we receive intelligence,
so do they.
We have a leak
But...
no one else will hear of this.
as you order, my bey.
According to Aktemur...
Romanos and his soldiers will get
horses from the Rum village.
I'll watch them with the alps.
Turgut.
Konur.
You will take care of the soldiers
waiting at the valley.
Then, we'll convince Nikola that
Romanos attacked us...
and we'll make him leave the castle.
It's our customs to answer traps
with traps.
True.
May Allah bless our jihad.
Amin, my bey.
Thank you!
Come on.
Wait.
Follow me.
You are making a trace.
Trackers!
Remove all the traces!
We left no trace, commander Romanos.
It's the opposite of whatever
you say, Romanos.
There will be a trace.
Don't mess around, commander!
You know the way.
Lead us!
Right away, sir!
In front of the Northern Walls
Alps!
What is this?
Are you giving up?
Conquest, we said!
Did you think it would be easy?
If the walls of İnegöl would go down
after a rock, it would be taken by others!
İnegöl is the fate of the ummah!
Don't forget, alps!
Fate loves endeavor!
Come on, valiants!
I don't want any mistakes!
Come on!
Come on, my lions!
Pull!
Show the same ability you
have with bows!
Pull! Pull!
Come on, alps!
Come on!
Release!
Allahu Akbar!
Pull! Pull!
Come on, alps!
Release!
You will not beat me!
This castle is mine!
These walls are mine!
You will not breach it!
You will not breach these walls!
Sir! Sir! They keep hitting the
walls at the same spot.
They never stop.
Then, what will you do?
You won't stop either!
Did they open a hole?
You will close that hole!
Do you get it, soldier?
Do you get it?
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Where are you Romanos?
Where are you?
They are removing their traces.
We need to be faster.
Alps, faster.
What is it, brother?
Cerkutay?
My bey, there are many ways and
no traces.
Since they didn't leave a trace all the
way, they are suspicious of us.
Alps, be cautious. It might be a trap.
Mashallah.
What is it, my bey?
My nephew.
He left a trace like my father
Ertuğrul Ghazi taught us.
Mashallah.
Come on.
Did you lose the way, idiot?
No, sir. I know these areas
very well.
It must've felt long
because we are on foot.
We have a missing.
Move.
Markus.
Where is Markus?
Soldiers, haven't anyone seen
Markus?
We haven't, sir. He was at
the end of the line.
You!
Markus was coming with you.
Didn't you see him?
No, sir. It's been a long time
since he left me.
I thought he went forward.
Where did this man go?
Sir, there is no time to search.
Maybe he fled.
No news from Commander Romanos.
Commander wanted us to wait.
He'll come.
I can't wait to spill Turkish blood.
They have the numbers.
We'll get the spotters with
arrows first.
Then, we'll attack altogether.
If Allah allows, we'll
destroy them, alps.
Inshallah, Turgut Bey.
We won't let anyone survive.
We'll attack from the rear, Kutan.
Alright, my bey.
You know what to do when
you see the signal.
We'll fight to the death.
May Allah bless our jihad.
Amin.
Alps. We'll go forward.
Come on.
I'm sorry for calling you an idiot.
It's not important,
Commander Romanos.
We are at war. We shouldn't be bothered
by such little things.
True.
How long how you been
in Bilecik Castle.
A year ago, I was sent by the Emperor's
regent to learn about Bilecik.
But before I get to learn,
Osman captured me.
Then, it was Regent Pericles.
Be careful.
He is a very dangerous man.
You shouldn't trust him.
Pericles wasn't the regent a year ago!
You are a traitor! You are a traitor!
Osman is following us.
Wait here and use this fool
as a bait.
You. You.
You will come with me.
We have no time to waste.
Don't come with me before
you kill them all.
Don't be sad, brother. Allah knows it,
maybe you'll see her again.
I was sad that you wouldn't
say farewell to her.
But you came in time.
You know it, brother. I'm not
good with farewells.
I know, brother.
I know.
Holafira understands it.
She sent her regards.
Alahaddin.
I'm glad to have you.
Who would support me if
not for you?
Don't let our other brothers
hear that and get jealous.
Don't tell them, brother.
It's enough for two of us
to know.
Alright, brother.
The guest girl dropped her
necklace in the tent.
Alahaddin.
This is Holafira's mother's necklace.
-Why would she leave it?
-She must've forgotten it, brother.
It has sentimental value.
She will be sad.
Brother.
You won't follow her because
of a necklace, will you?
My father will find a way when
he returns.
Come on!
My shehzad.
You scared me, Baysungur Alp.
What are you doing here? Where is
your brother?
You were supposed to be training
Alright, then. Find your brother.
Get your weapons and come to drill.
We'll come after I find my brother.
Inshallah.
Oh, brother, oh.
I almost lied because of you.
With the name of Allah.
Come on! Come on!
You won't succeed!
Osman Bey will send you all to hell!
You will go there before us, Turk.
My nephew!
Romanos got him.
Alps. Be cautious.
This might be a trap.
You know what to do.
Come on.
Boran. Take him out.
Yes, my bey.
-My nephew.
-My bey.
-Are you alright?
-I am, my bey.
Brothers, archer formation!
Come on.
My bey, Romanos is going to his
soldiers at the valley.
Alps. Go to the valley.
I'll go after Romanos.
As you order, my bey.
My nephew.
My Aktemur.
Are you alright?
Thank you, Boran Alp.
My father was right about you.
Mashallah.
Brothers, we are going to the valley.
Come on!
Come on, alps!
It's time to keep our word to Osman Bey!
Allah is righteous!
Where are you going, Romanos?
Are you in a hurry?
So, you found me.
Are you going to your soldiers
at the valley?
Do you think that you still
have soldiers.
Do you think that I would
come here with a bunch of soldiers?
I'm not like those lords.
I'm not like anyone.
Attack.
Run, Romanos.
Run.
Where are you running to?
Who did ever get away
from me?
Where are you?
My Allah, watch over my brother.
Come on!
Kayı Tribe declared war on İnegöl, sir.
We poisoned the provisions to the quarters
instead of the tribe.
They aren't my aunt's soldiers.
I must inform the tribe at once.
Where is Master Darius?
We were supposed to talk to him.
Master Darius died.
Osman killed him.
How could this happen?
What are we waiting for?
Let's burn Kayı Tribe!
Leave no living there!
She is running away!
Hurry! Follow her!
Stop! Don't run!
They'll kill Osman Bey's soldiers.
-Holafira!
-Orhan!
What's happening here?
They aren't my aunt's soldiers.
Your enemies.
Hide behind me!
Ya Allah!
I'm here, brother.
My valiant brother.
They poisoned the provisions
going to the alps.
We must inform them.
If we can't get there in time,
we'll lose the siege.
Alahaddin, inform our mothers.
I won't leave you, brother.
Brother, go and inform our mothers.
Where are those?
You will be the guarantee of my exit
From these cursed Turkish lands
Only your corpse will
get out of this land!
Take him!
Don't be afraid, neither father
nor mother will leave us here.
Alaeddin will catch up.
I know.
I am not afraid.
Brothers!
Romanos escaped...
...but he cannot go back to
the castle like that.
Nikola's plan is wasted.
His time is over.
It's our turn now.
Right now...
The catapults headed by Gündüz Bey...
...strike the castle walls
day and night.
But, we will not wait for a breach.
Aktemur.
You will enter the castle
with a couple alps.
You will say Romanos will
attack us before sunrise.
Nikola will leave the castle with his
soldiers after hearing this.
The rest will kill Nikola and his soldiers.
In that case, my nephew Aktemur
will break the bridges and open the gates.
Inshallah,(If Allah permits)
Turgut Bey.
This is our aim.
But we will still be cautious.
Because when the bridges are open...
They'll notice Aktemur.
When Aktemur gives us the sign...
...we'll break the gates
with battering jam.
My Bey.
What is going to happen to Aktemur
and his alps in that case?
Gunduz Bey is worried
about this too.
That's why he will place
stairs...
...climb up to the castle
and attack.
After he attracts
Nikola and his soldiers...
...the bridge and gates will
be open for us.
We will not leave Aktemur alone.
My Bey, who are the alps
to join Aktemur?
My Bey, if you will excuse us, we want to
enter the castle with our brother Aktemur.
We'll open the bridge and the gates,
even if it costs our lives, my Bey.
We want this mission.
Eyvallah.
(Thank you)
So wear your equipments!
- As you order, my Bey.
We pounced on Ingul like a claw
From behind the walls
And from above
and from the gates
and behind the gates!
We will attack from all sides!
It is time to slaughter!
Alps!
Come on.
Mother!
Stop, mother!
Alaeddin!
Son!
Son, what's it?
What is it?
Mother, my mother!
Alaeddin, son!
What happened? Where is Orhan?
Tell me.
They might have kidnapped
my brother Orhan and Holoferi.
What are you talking about Alaeddin?
Who kidnapped Orhan and why?
The ones who came to get Holoferi
were not her aunt's men, mother.
They were enemy.
They poisoned the provisions
of alps.
Ignobles! They can't dare to duel,
they try poisoning!
Save my brother, mother.
He is alone.
They might have been kidnapped.
We will save them, son.
We will save your brother.
Kumral Abdal, destroy the provisions.
Go and inform the quarters
with sisters.
My Alaeddin is entrusted to you.
We will go to save Orhan
with Baysungur Alp.
Don't worry.
Baysungur Alp!
Come, my valiant.
Come on now!
Go!
Selvi!
Barkin!
Barkin, you came just in time.
Selvi, what's happening here?
Where are the Hatuns going?
They went to save Orhan. The ones who came
for Holofire turned out to be enemies.
- Husamettin!
- My Bey!
Take Alps and deploy
where Osman Bey told you to.
We'll go to Hatuns with Selvi.
Come.
Sisters, dig a hole.
Bury the poisonous provisions.
Hurry.
Pull pull pull pull!
Straighten it!
Come on lions!
O Haqq!
Allah is the greatest!
Come on come on come on!
Come on.
Allah is the greatest!
Run!
Inform Lord Nikola!
The walls are crunching!
Come on valiants!
Come on lions!
Come on!
Speak up!
Sir, the north walls are
demolished heavily.
They are cracking.
They shall not crack!
Do you understand?
If the walls crack, army cracks.
If army cracks, we crack!
Do you understand me!?
If that happens,
I will not let Osman's alps to kill you.
I will strangle you with my hands!
With my hands!
Get out.
Get out!
Get out all!
This castle will not fall.
It will not fall.
Osman.
Death will be your escape...
...after what I do to you!
Come on now.
Come to me.
Are you all Osman could send?
Osman?
No sir. I am not Osman's man.
I am his enemy.
You must be one of the
Rome commanders.
Right.
But you are missing.
I am the most famous, the most relentless
commander Romanus!
What about you?
Osman's enemy.
Who are you?
Who is your name?
How can I be sure?
I was Master Arius' closest man,
may God bless him.
My real name is Aizek.
Arius.
I saw his head in a bag.
Aizek,
Aizek, Aizek, Aizek, Aizek.
A sign that only Arius' men carry.
So you are on my side.
I forget my friends.
But I never forget my enemies.
Osman.
I will never forget his face.
I will make him pay for all the
things he did to us!
I don't know how long I'll live,
Commander Romanus.
But I swear that...
I'll avenge for Master Arius before I die.
And I will serve for his case.
Flare your hatred.
You will be with me while I skin Osman !
I can't wait to see that moment, sir.
May our war be blessed.
Eyvallah.
Come on!
Pull!
Allah is the greatest!
Pull pull pull pull!
Come on!
Come on brother!
Throw!
Allah is the greatest!
Come on my valiants!
Come on valiants!
Come on alps!
Pull pull pull!
Come on!
Cerkutay.
That castle will be conquered tonight!
Come on, come on!
Come on valiants!
Remember the promise we gave to Osman Bey!
Come on!
Allah is the greatest!
Throw!
Help!
Allah is the greatest!
Masha Allah! (praise be!)
As long as we have that much brave men,
we will not leave any unconquered castle!
This is what Ertugrul Ghazi's son can do!
We learned from the master,
from you Master Davut!
- Eyvallah! (thank you)
- Welcome!
Throw!
Allah is eternal!
Come on!
Come on valiants!
Come on pull!
Pull pull pull pull!
Back!
Now!
You came with luck, Master Davut!
- Masha Allah! (praise be)
- Thank Allah!
Allah is the greatest!
O Allah's Muhammed!
We saw that they are not indestructible.
Thank Allah.
Prepare Kayi flags, alps!
Time has come.
Inshallah Konur, Inshallah!
We attacked the first.
Our path is open now.
Our path is open thanks to Allah!
Konur, Boran, time to attack.
Aktemur is inside.
This attack is a gift for me, Boran!
You'll kill the infidels of Nikola
in there.
- Come on my valiants.
- As you order, my Bey.
As you order, Gunduz Bey.
What about me, my Bey?
Your place is my side, Cerkutay!
My side!
Eyvallah my Bey!
Tell us to break, tell us to destroy!
Destroy, Cerkutay!
Let's make a breach!
Break them!
Come on!
So what we need to do
is to make a breach.
Come on! Come on!
O Haqq!
Praise be!
My Bey, this is for you!
Fill it!
Come on my lion!
Back!
Come on!
O Haqq!
Allah is the greatest!
Praise be!
My Bey, this one is yours.
O Haqq!
Allah is the greatest!
Come on Alps.
We'll shoot our arrows and never stop.
In the name of Allah.
Who are you?
I am Alexander.
I brought news from Commander Romanus.
Now.
Open the bridge!
Turks are after us!
Now.
Come on open the gates!
Open the gates!
Come on Alps!
How is the situation?
They took the bait.
The gates are open for Aktemur, Osman Bey.
Eyvallah, eyvallah.
Praise be to Aktemur.
Praise be so.
We have been waiting for this moment for
a long time.
We have been through a lot.
Thank Allah, we managed.
We are closer to the infidels
than their breath, Osman Bey.
Turkmen Beys are blinded outside
because they are always busy inside.
But you are not like that.
You always backed me up.
The path is tough.
But your brotherhood is tougher.
Thank you.
I was bull-headed, Osman Bey.
You taught me how to unite.
Now I know...
...as long as we are united,
we'll break every gates.
We'll proceed like a battering ram.
I know it now.
Turks will not rest from now on.
We are on a path where...
...you fall behind if you don't
force yourself to proceed.
Then...
...we'll always go forward, Osman Bey!
Always go forward.
You came this far, Kumral Abdal.
What's the problem?
The enemy is inside the tribe, Osman Bey.
They poisoned the provisions of Alps.
What are you saying, Kumral Abdal?
Where are the Hatuns?
What is Alaeddin doing here?
My Bey...
...my brother and Holofira are
kidnapped by the enemy.
Don't worry, nephew.
We'll have them back safe and sound.
Alaeddin informed us.
Bala Hatun sent us here.
We destroyed the poisonous
provisions.
Hatuns and Barkin Bey
went after Orhan.
Alaeddin, go rest, nephew.
As you command, uncle.
Come on.
Alexander?
We did it, Lord Nikola!
Commander Romanos got his troop.
This is good news!
Listen to me.
This is some good news, Alexander!
Commander Romanos wanted me to inform you.
They are waiting for the troops of castle
to attack the quarters.
Everything is going by your plan.
We are not going to wait any longer.
We will act immediately!
Now!
Yes sir.
Hurry.
Good.
My Bey.
Nikola's support troop is
out of the castle.
Good.
They trust their number.
But Konur and Boran...
...are waiting in ambush to crush them.
They'll understand who we are...
...once they are trampled
under our horses.
Is Nikola on the command?
No, my Bey.
There's another commander on the command.
He sends his soldiers to death...
...and hide in the back.
Ignoble.
Inshallah he doesn't disappear.
We need him.
Our preparations are complete.
He will first lose his soldiers.
Then his sword.
Then his life.
From now on...
...nothing can save him from death.
Nothing.
Let them come, Konur.
Let them die under
the glorious horses of Turks.
We haven't been able to enter inside...
...but destroying them from outside
is improtant too.
Yes brother.
Valiants, get ready!
Hold tight the reins!
Hold them tight!
Swing your sword to toss them!
Infantries are coming from Inegol.
Brothers!
Time has come!
Allah is the greatest!
Now!
Time has come.
May our war be blessed.
Allah is the greatest!
Turhan, I got the right.
Left is yours, brother.
Allah is the greatest!
They are approaching!
- Allah is the greatest!
Shields!
Open!
The end of the road, Osman
You will pay the price
And then you will die
You will die.
I will grow up.
They are coming, sir
What are you talking about, soldier?
Turks, Turks are coming, sir.
Turks are at the gates!
How can this happen?
Damn, is that impossible?
How can it happen?
Allah is the greatest!
Amen.
In the name of of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
O our great Allah, make Your
Messenger, his companions,
and all the saints and
martyrs a support for our army
Amen.
- Make our army victorious.
- Amen.
- Let us conquer Inegol!
Fatiha
My Allah!
Praise our Prophet and his ancestry.
In the name of of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Acknowledge that...
There is no God but Allah.
Open!
Allah is the greatest!
There is no God but Allah.
Death is a day,
and that day is today, valiants!
Allah is the greatest!
Even if I can't make it to tomorrow,
it has been an honor, Osman Bey.
Today, we we are not going to die.
The state needs a head!
- We still have a lot to do!
- Eyvallah!
Come on Alps!
Open!
Allah is eternal!
Close!
Open!
Do not let them through the gates!
They are crowded.
Come on!
Allah is the greatest!
Bring the battering ram!
Come on valiants!
Go on lions!
Come on brothers!
Break it!
Allah is eternal!
Hit it, valiants!
Hit it!
Come on valiants!
Break the gates of infidels!
Hit, valiants!
Open!
Now!
Come on alps!
We'll enter the cave of infidels!
O Allah!
Allah is the greatest!
There is no God but Allah!
There is no God but Allah
Allah is victorious.
Speak, soldier!
Osman and his men
entered the castle through the main gate!
They are in!
Soldier!
Defend!
Only their corpses will enter this castle!
Only corpses!
Our faces will be the last faces
Osman and his alps see!
- Is it clear?
- Yes sir!
Come on brothers!
Come on!
Hit them!
"Help from Allah and a victory near at hand;
Allah is victorious!
and give good news to the believers.
O Muhammed"
[Surah As-Saff 13]
Allah is victorious!
- Ignoble dogs!
- What are we going to do?
Allah is victorious!
They ruined the battering jam.
Brothers!
We need to pull it.
Come on my valiants!
Open!
Attack!
Nikola.
Nikola!
There is no turning back now.
This is going to be over today.
Come on brothers!
Stay strong.
Pull the battering ram, alps!
Pull!
Come on valiants!
"but Allah"
Allah is eternal!
Back!
"but Allah"
Allah is eternal!
Allah is right!
Inegol will be your grave, Osman Bey!
Your grave!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com